with a firm belief in the power of unity
we embarked on a transformative journey
to Champion diversity equity and
inclusion step into the inspiring world
of all okay please a thriving initiative
driven by the collective efforts of
employees committed to make a difference
in an extraordinary Pursuit we curated a
vibrant Street play competition ICICI
bombard run Munch
Nar igniting the passion and showcasing
the remarkable talents of our Workforce
fostering the culture of artistic
expression and
collaboration normally we see a natak or
Street Place only in college and having
it in an organization setup I think I
have seen it in the first time of my 10
years career here out of numerous
exceptional teams four was selected to
perform at various icic Lombard offices
across India Mumbai Delhi Hyderabad and
Kolkata it was a light mode act happy to
see such uh initiative taken by our
company to educate us to remove our
differences and stereotypical views
aside addressing Dei biases each team
showcased their powerful performances
their plays were thought-provoking
gender bias personal comments lack of
empathy and Regional
stereotype the stage came alive with the
boundless Talent of our Workforce
delivering mesmerizing performances that
conveyed impactful messages on Dei that
left everyone's Spell bound and we look
forward to many such uh n so that we can
it helps us in gaining much more
insights about the virtues and uh the
culture that the company carries ICI
Lombards rangmunch narak is a sh in
example of our commitment towards
creating an inclusive
environment let's join hands and take a
bold step forward embracing diversity
Equity inclusion with a promise to
create a bias-free workplace
[Music]
together